(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) The birds chirp.
The alarm clock rings.
She wakes up.
She stretches her arms out.
She yawns.
She gives herself two hours to get ready.
She has a very important day at school.
She washes her face.
She brushes her teeth.
She goes outside.
She takes a breath of fresh air.
She jogs for 20 minutes.
She goes back in the house.
She makes scrambled eggs and sausage.
It is delicious.
Her little brother asks for some.
She gives what was left over to him.
She goes back to her room.
She opens up her history textbook.
She has a quiz today.
She quickly goes over the important details.
She goes to class.